Indiana University President's Office Correspondence, 1913-1937 C286
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1913-1937 (Box 1)
  - Rey (Box 220)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 220)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 220)
  - Reynolds, Jack—contract, 1923 (Box 220)
  - Rh (Box 220)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 220)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 220)
  - Rha-Rhi, 1913-1923 (Box 220)
  - Rho-Rhy, 1913-1923 (Box 220)
  - Rhodes Scholarships (Box 220)
    - (Hollingsworth), 1916 (Box 220)
    - Memoranda, rules, forms, 1903-1932 (Box 220)
    - 1918-1928 (Box 220)
    - 1928-1937 (Box 220)
  - Rhodes Trust (Box 220)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 220)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 220)
    - 1923-1931 (Box 220)
    - 1931-1936 (Box 220)
  - Ri (Box 221)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 221)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 221)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 221)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 221)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 221)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 221)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 221)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 221)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 221)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 221)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 221)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 221)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 221)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 221)
  - Ri-Rof, 1928-1929 (Box 221)
  - Ria-Ric (Box 221)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 221)
    - 1916-1920 (Box 221)
  - Ria-Ric (Box 222)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 222)
  - Richardson, 1913-1923 (Box 222)
  - Riche, 1923-1937 (Box 222)
  - Rid (Box 222)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 222)
    - 1928-1937 (Box 222)
  - Rid-Rie, 1913-1923 (Box 222)
  - Ridgway, Robert, 23 February 1925 (Box 222)
  - Rif-Ril, 1913-1923 (Box 222)
  - Riker, Dorothy, 1926-1929 (Box 222)
  - Ril (Box 222)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 222)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 222)
  - Riley Memorial Hospital (Box 222)
    - 1920-1922 (Box 222)
  - Riley Memorial Hospital (Box 223)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 223)
    - 1923-1925), (2 folders (Box 223)
    - 1925-1928 (Box 223)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 223)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 223)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 223)
    - 1932-1935 (Box 223)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 223)
    - Contractors, architects, etc., 1921-1921 (Box 223)
    - Per diem claim, 1928-1928 (Box 223)
    - Rotary newsletters, 1930-1930 (Box 223)
  - Riley, James Whitcomb, 1915-1917 (Box 223)
  - Riley Memorial Association (Box 223)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 223)
    - Dinner, 1924 (Box 223)
  - Rim-Ris, 1913-1923 (Box 223)
  - Ris, 1922-1937 (Box 223)
  - Rit-Riz, 1913-1923 (Box 223)
  - Ro (Box 223)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 223)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 223)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 223)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 223)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 223)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 223)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 223)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 223)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 223)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 223)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 223)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 223)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 223)
  - Ro (Box 224)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 224)
  - Roa-Rob (Box 224)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 224)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 224)
  - Roberts (Box 224)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 224)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 224)
  - Roberts, Harvey, 1915 (Box 224)
  - Robertston-Robinson (Box 224)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 224)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 224)
  - Robertson, N.A., 1918-1919 (Box 224)
  - Robi (Box 224)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 224)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 224)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 224)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 224)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 224)
  - Robinson, Colonel O.P. (Box 224)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 224)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 224)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 224)
  - Robinson, Colonel O.P., 1931-1932; (2 folders (Box 224)
  - Robinson, Professor D.S., 1934-1937 (Box 224)
  - Robinson, Professor J.J., 1934-1937 (Box 224)
  - Roc (Box 224)
    - 1913-1926 (Box 224)
  - Roc (Box 225)
    - 1926-1937 (Box 225)
  - Rod-Roe, 1913-1923 (Box 225)
  - Roddy, Mary, 1913-1937 (Box 225)
  - Roe (Box 225)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 225)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 225)
  - Rof-Rog (Box 225)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 225)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 225)
  - Rog-Rz, 1928-1929 (Box 225)
  - Rogers, Will—Memorial Campaign, 1935-1936 (Box 225)
  - Roh, 1923-1937 (Box 225)
  - Roh-Rol, 1913-1923 (Box 225)
  - Rom, 1923-1937 (Box 225)
  - Romance Languages, Department of, 1913-1932 (Box 225)
  - Rom-Ror, 1913-1923 (Box 225)
  - Roo (Box 225)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 225)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 225)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 225)
  - Rooms for men, 1916-1917 (Box 225)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1936 (Box 225)
  - Ros (Box 225)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 225)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 225)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 225)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 225)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 225)
  - Rose, T.F. (Box 225)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 225)
    - 1916-1919 (Box 225)
  - Rosen (Box 225)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 225)
  - Rosen (Box 226)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 226)
  - Ross (Box 226)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 226)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 226)
  - Rot-Rov, 1913-1918 (Box 226)
  - Rot, 1923-1926 (Box 226)
  - Rot (Box 226)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 226)
    - 1929-1933 (Box 226)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 226)
  - Rot-Rov (Box 226)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 226)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 226)
  - Rotary Club—Bloomington, 1927-1937 (Box 226)
  - Rothrock, D.A. (Box 226)
    - 1913-1924 (Box 226)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 226)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 226)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 226)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 226)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 226)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 226)
  - Row, 1923-1937 (Box 226)
  - Row-Roz, 1913-1923 (Box 227)
  - Rowlands, Edward (Box 227)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 227)
    - October 1926-December 1927 (Box 227)
    - January-September 1928 (Box 227)
    - September 1928-April 1929 (Box 227)
    - May-September 1929 (Box 227)
    - September 1929-April 1930 (Box 227)
    - May-September 1930 (Box 227)
    - September 1930-February 1931 (Box 227)
    - March-August 1931 (Box 227)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 227)
    - Personal, 1928-1928 (Box 227)
  - Royal, Perle C., 1924-1929 (Box 227)
  - Ru (Box 227)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 227)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 227)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 227)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 227)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 227)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 227)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 227)
  - Rua-Ruc, 1913-1923 (Box 227)
  - Rud-Rue, 1913-1923 (Box 228)
  - Rue, 1923-1937 (Box 228)
  - Ruf-Rum, 1913-1923 (Box 228)
  - Run-Rur, 1913-1923 (Box 228)
  - Rus (Box 228)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 228)
    - 1920-1925 (Box 228)
    - 1925-1928 (Box 228)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 228)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 228)
  - Rush rules, 1936-1937 (Box 228)
  - Russell, 1913-1923 (Box 228)
  - Russell, John Dale, 1922-1935 (Box 228)
  - Russi, 1924 (Box 228)
  - Rut-Ruz, 1913-1923 (Box 228)
  - Ry (Box 228)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 228)
    - 1926-1931 (Box 228)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 228)
  - Rya, 1913-1923 (Box 228)
  - Rye, 1913-1923 (Box 228)
  - S (Box 228)
    - 1914-1922 (Box 228)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 228)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 228)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 228)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 228)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 228)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 228)
  - Saa-Sak, 1913-1923 (Box 229)
  - Sa-Scq, 1928-1929 (Box 229)
  - Sackett, R.L., 1913-1915 (Box 229)
  - Sage, Elizabeth—acting head, 1926-1927 (Box 229)
  - Sal (Box 229)
    - 1913-1923 (Box 229)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 229)
    - 1929-1933 (Box 229)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 229)
  - Salary notices, 1928 (Box 229)
  - Salary roll, 1936-1937 (Box 229)
  - Salvation Army, 1914-1921 (Box 229)
  - Sam (Box 229)
    - 1913-1928 (Box 229)
    - 1928-1937 (Box 229)
  - Sample, Mary, 1914-1928 (Box 229)
  - Sample, Mary Alice, 1923-1937 (Box 229)
  - San (Box 229)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 229)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 229)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 229)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 229)
    - 1932-1935 (Box 229)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 229)
  - San-Saq (Box 229)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 229)
    - 1917-1923 (Box 229)
  - Sanders, Chauncey, 1926-1937 (Box 229)
  - Sanders, Newell, 1930-1937 (Box 229)
  - Sandi, 1924-1927 (Box 229)
  - Sandison, Howard, 1916-1919 (Box 229)
  - Sar, 1923-1937 (Box 229)
  - Sar-Sav, 1913-1923 (Box 230)
  - Sargent, E.H. & Company (Box 230)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 230)
    - 1916-1923 (Box 230)
  - Sav, 1923-1937 (Box 230)
  - Saw-Saz, 1913-1923 (Box 230)
  - Sayles, Nathaniel Louis, 1932-1936 (Box 230)
  - Sc (Box 230)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 230)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 230)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 230)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 230)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 230)
  - Sca-Sce, 1913-1923 (Box 230)
  - Sch (Box 230)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 230)
    - 1929-1937 (Box 230)
  - Sch-Sd, 1928-1929 (Box 230)
  - Scha, 1913-1923 (Box 230)
  - Schaf, 1923-1934 (Box 230)
  - Sche (Box 230)
    - 1913-1921 (Box 230)
    - 1921-1926 (Box 230)
    - 1926-1930 (Box 230)
  - Scheifley, William H. (Box 230)
    - 1918-1927 (Box 230)
    - 1928-1937 (Box 230)
  - Schi (Box 230)
    - 1913-1925 (Box 230)
  - Schi (Box 231)
    - 1925-1937 (Box 231)
  - Schl (Box 231)
    - 1913-1925 (Box 231)
    - 1925-1937 (Box 231)
  - Schlafer, George E., 1921-1937 (Box 231)
  - Schm (Box 231)
    - 1914-1927 (Box 231)
    - 1927-1937 (Box 231)
  - Schn (Box 231)
    - 1913-1921 (Box 231)
    - 1921-1929 (Box 231)
    - 1929-1937 (Box 231)
  - Scho (Box 231)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 231)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 231)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 231)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 231)
    - 1930-1934 (Box 231)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 231)
  - School of Business Administration—correspondence regarding New Deal, 1934-1935 (Box 231)
  - School of Education (Box 231)
    - Application of companies for work or furnish materials, 1936-1937 (Box 231)
    - Education and Laboratory Building—re: hardware (Pierson-Lewis Hardware Company), 1936-1937 (Box 231)
    - Letters urging new building, 1935-1935 (Box 231)
    - Building to be built under P.W.A., 1936-1937 (Box 231)
  - School of Medicine (Box 231)
    - 1914-1920 (Box 231)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 231)
      - 1928-1930 (Box 231)
      - 1930-1931 (Box 231)
  - School of Medicine (Box 232)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 232)
      - 1931-1932 (Box 232)
      - June-September 1933 (Box 232)
      - September 1932-May 1933 (Box 232)
      - September 1933-May 1934 (Box 232)
      - May-September 1934 (Box 232)
      - 1934-1935 (Box 232)
      - 1935-1936 (Box 232)
      - 1936-1937 (Box 232)
    - Hospital Survey, 1930 (Box 232)
    - Salary rolls, 1932-1932 (Box 232)
  - See also: Medicine, School of (Box 232)
  - School of Medicine Building (Box 232)
    - Applications for materials, 1935-1935 (Box 232)
    - Correspondence regarding construction (Box 232)
      - 1935-1936 (Box 232)
      - 1936-1937 (Box 232)
  - Schmidt, 1913-1923 (Box 232)
  - Schr (Box 232)
    - 1913-1925 (Box 232)
    - 1925-1937 (Box 232)
  - Schroeder, 1914-1923 (Box 232)
  - Schu (Box 232)
    - 1913-1921 (Box 232)
    - 1921-1927 (Box 232)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 232)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 232)
  - Schult, 1923-1937 (Box 232)
  - Schum, 1923-1937 (Box 233)
  - Schw (Box 233)
    - 1913-1923 (Box 233)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 233)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 233)
  - Schweers, Richard Henry, 1931-1937 (Box 233)
  - Sci, 1913-1923 (Box 233)
  - Scientific Materials Company, 1913-1917 (Box 233)
  - Sco (Box 233)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 233)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 233)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 233)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 233)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 233)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 233)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 233)
  - Sco-Scy (Box 233)
    - 1913-1915 (Box 233)
    - 1915-1917 (Box 233)
    - 1917-1920 (Box 233)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 233)
  - Scholarships—country, 1925-1926 (Box 233)
  - Scott, Will (Box 233)
    - 1927-1931 (Box 233)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 233)
  - Se (Box 234)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 234)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 234)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 234)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 234)
    - 1932-1935 (Box 234)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 234)
  - Se-Shd, 1928-1929 (Box 234)
  - Sea-Sek (Box 234)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 234)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 234)
  - Sears, Roebuck & Company (Box 234)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 234)
    - 1923-1937 (Box 234)
  - Searey, William A., 1915-1917 (Box 234)
  - Sec, 1923-1937 (Box 234)
  - Sei, 1923-1937 (Box 234)
  - Seibert, Fred R., 1914 (Box 234)
  - Sel (Box 234)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 234)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 234)
  - Sel-Sem, 1913-1920 (Box 234)
  - Selleck, Roda E., 1923 (Box 234)
  - Sembower, Charles J. (Box 234)
    - 1913-1927 (Box 234)
    - 1927-1937 (Box 234)
  - Sen-Sez (Box 234)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 234)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 234)
  - Senior Class Memorial of 1919, 1920-1921 (Box 235)
  - Senior Class Election of Officers regarding the merit system, 1936-1937 (Box 235)
  - Ser, 1923-1937 (Box 235)
  - Set, 1923-1931 (Box 235)
  - Sh (Box 235)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 235)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 235)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 235)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 235)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 235)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 235)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 235)
  - Sha (Box 235)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 235)
    - 1917-1921 (Box 235)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 235)
  - Shan (Box 235)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 235)
    - 1929-1937 (Box 235)
  - Shar (Box 235)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 235)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 235)
  - Shav, 1923-1937 (Box 235)
  - Shaw, William Asbury, 1931-1937 (Box 235)
  - Shaw-Walker Company, 1913-1915 (Box 235)
  - Shea, J.H., 1913-1919 (Box 235)
  - She (Box 235)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 235)
    - 1917-1921 (Box 235)
  - She (Box 236)
    - 1921-1924 (Box 236)
    - 1924-1928 (Box 236)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 236)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 236)
  - She-Shz, 1928-1929 (Box 236)
  - Shel, 1923-1937 (Box 236)
  - Sher (Box 236)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 236)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 236)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 236)
  - Fort Sheridan Camp, 1918 (Box 236)
  - Sheridan, Lawrence V., 1923-1935 (Box 236)
  - Shi (Box 236)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 236)
    - 1917-1919 (Box 236)
    - 1919-1925 (Box 236)
    - 1925-1928 (Box 236)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 236)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 236)
  - Shively, B.F., 1913-1917 (Box 236)
  - Shl, 1919-1920 (Box 236)
  - Sho (Box 236)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 236)
  - Sho (Box 237)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 237)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 237)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 237)
  - Sho-Shr (Box 237)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 237)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 237)
  - Shockley, Frank W., 1914-1922 (Box 237)
  - Shockley, Mrs. J.W., 1918 (Box 237)
  - Shu-Shy, 1913-1923 (Box 237)
  - Si (Box 237)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 237)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 237)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 237)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 237)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 237)
  - Si-Sn, 1928-1929 (Box 237)
  - Sia-Sik (Box 237)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 237)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 237)
  - Siebenthal, Mrs. A.J.—correspondence concerning house rented to university, 1925-1926 (Box 237)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1914-1917 (Box 237)
  - Sigma Chi, 1913-1918 (Box 237)
  - Sigma Delta Chi, 1916-1937 (Box 237)
  - Sigma Kappa, 1918 (Box 237)
  - Sigma Nu, undated (Box 237)
  - Sigma XI, 1914-1916 (Box 237)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon Fraternity—Louden House rental correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 237)
  - Sil (Box 237)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 237)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 237)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 237)
  - Sim (Box 238)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 238)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 238)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 238)
  - Sima-Simo, 1913-1923 (Box 238)
  - Simo, 1923-1937 (Box 238)
  - Simp-Simz, 1913-1923 (Box 238)
  - Sin (Box 238)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 238)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 238)
  - Sin-Siz, 1913-1923 (Box 238)
  - Sk (Box 238)
    - 1913-1923 (Box 238)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 238)
    - 1928-1933 (Box 238)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 238)
  - Sl (Box 238)
    - 1913-1921 (Box 238)
  - Sl (Box 238)
    - 1921-1926 (Box 238)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 238)
    - 1929-1933 (Box 238)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 238)
  - Sle, 1923-1937 (Box 239)
  - Slipher, Vesto M., 1913-1937 (Box 239)
  - Sm (Box 239)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 239)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 239)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 239)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 239)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 239)
  - Smit, 1923-1937 (Box 239)
  - Smith (Box 239)
    - A-E (Box 239)
      - 1913-1919 (Box 239)
      - 1919-1923 (Box 239)
    - A-K (Box 239)
      - 1923-1925 (Box 239)
      - 1925-1927 (Box 239)
      - 1927-1928 (Box 239)
      - 1928-1930 (Box 239)
      - 1930-1932 (Box 239)
      - 1932-1934 (Box 239)
      - 1934-1936 (Box 239)
      - 1936-1937 (Box 239)
  - Smith College, 1915-1918 (Box 240)
  - Smith Electric Company, 1923-1925 (Box 240)
  - Smith, H.L. (Box 240)
    - 1915-1916 (Box 240)
    - 1916-1919 (Box 240)
  - Smith, H.L. (Box 240)
    - 1921-1922 (Box 240)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 240)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 240)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 240)
    - September 1925-March 1926 (Box 240)
    - April-June 1926 (Box 240)
    - July-August 1926 (Box 240)
    - September 1926-February 1927 (Box 240)
    - March-September 1927 (Box 240)
    - September 1927-May 1928 (Box 240)
  - Smith, H.L. (Box 241)
  - June-September, 1928 (Box 241)
    - September 1928-May 1929 (Box 241)
    - June-September 1929 (Box 241)
    - September 1929-May 1930 (Box 241)
    - June-September 1930 (Box 241)
    - September 1930-May 1931 (Box 241)
    - June 1931-January 1932 (Box 241)
    - February-September 1932 (Box 241)
    - September 1932-May 1933 (Box 241)
    - June-December 1933 (Box 241)
    - January-September 1934 (Box 241)
    - September 1934-April 1935 (Box 241)
    - May-December 1935 (Box 241)
    - January-September 1936 (Box 241)
  - Smith, H.L. (Box 242)
    - September 1936-April 1937 (Box 242)
    - May-September 1937 (Box 242)
  - Smith (Box 242)
    - F-K (Box 242)
      - 1913-1918 (Box 242)
      - 1918-1923 (Box 242)
    - L-G, 1913-1917 (Box 242)
    - L-Q, 1918-1922 (Box 242)
    - L-Z (Box 242)
      - 1923-1925 (Box 242)
      - 1925-1927 (Box 242)
      - 1927-1929 (Box 242)
      - 1929-1931 (Box 242)
      - 1931-1933 (Box 242)
      - 1933-1935 (Box 242)
      - 1935-1937 (Box 242)
    - R-Z (Box 242)
      - 1913-1918 (Box 242)
      - 1918-1923 (Box 242)
  - L.C. Smith and Company, 1918-1935 (Box 242)
  - Smith, S.E. (Box 242)
    - 1915-1920 (Box 242)
  - Smith, S.E. (Box 243)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 243)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 243)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 243)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 243)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 243)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 243)
  - Smith, U.H. (Box 243)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 243)
    - 1918-1919 (Box 243)
    - 1919-1921 (Box 243)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 243)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 243)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 243)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 243)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 243)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 243)
  - Smith, U.H. (Box 244)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 244)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 244)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 244)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 244)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 244)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 244)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 244)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 244)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 244)
    - Report of finances made in the bursar's office, 1931-1932 (Box 244)
  - Smith, Virginia Elmeria, 1932-1937 (Box 244)
  - Smo, 1924-1937 (Box 244)
  - Sn (Box 244)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 244)
    - 1918-1922 (Box 244)
    - 1922-1926 (Box 244)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 244)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 244)
    - 1932-1936 (Box 244)
  - Sn (Box 245)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 245)
  - Snedeker, Caroline, 1920 (Box 245)
  - Snider and Rotz, 1920-1921 (Box 245)
  - Sniff, L.N., 1913-1918 (Box 245)
  - Snoddy, George S. (Box 245)
    - Acting head, 1928 (Box 245)
    - Secretary of psychology department, 1933-1934 (Box 245)
  - So (Box 245)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 245)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 245)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 245)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 245)
  - So-Ss, 1928-1929 (Box 245)
  - Soa-Sol, 1913-1923 (Box 245)
  - Social Affairs, Rules Regulating, 1914-1915 (Box 245)
  - Social Service Department (Box 245)
    - ca. 1915 (Box 245)
    - 1915-1917 (Box 245)
  - Sol, 1923-1937 (Box 245)
  - Soldiers Bonus Campaign, 1930 (Box 245)
  - Soldiers' letters, 1918 (Box 245)
  - Soldiers of the Soil, undated (Box 245)
  - Sollitt, Ralph, 1914-1918 (Box 245)
  - Son, 1923-1937 (Box 245)
  - Som-Sop, 1913-1923 (Box 245)
  - Sor-Soz (Box 245)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 245)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 245)
  - Sou (Box 245)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 245)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 245)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 245)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 245)
  - Sou (Box 246)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 246)
  - South Dakota, University of, 1913-1918 (Box 246)
  - South Hall, undated (Box 246)
  - South Western Publishing Company, 1916-1917 (Box 246)
  - Southern Indiana Sporting Goods, 1930-1933 (Box 246)
  - Sp (Box 246)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 246)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 246)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 246)
    - 1932-1935 (Box 246)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 246)
  - Spa-Spe (Box 246)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 246)
    - 1918-1921 (Box 246)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 246)
  - Spalding, A.G. and Brothers, 1913-1918 (Box 246)
  - Spalding and Brothers, 1923-1937 (Box 246)
  - Spe (Box 246)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 246)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 246)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 246)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 246)
  - Spencer Lens Company, 1914-1919 (Box 246)
  - Sph, 1918-1923 (Box 246)
  - Sphung, A.A., 1913-1914 (Box 246)
  - Spi (Box 246)
    - 1913-1926 (Box 246)
    - 1926-1931 (Box 246)
  - Spi (Box 247)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 247)
  - Spo-Spy, 1913-1923 (Box 247)
  - Spr (Box 247)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 247)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 247)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 247)
  - Sq, 1913-1931 (Box 247)
  - St-Sz, 1913-1914 (Box 247)
  - St (Box 247)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 247)
    - 1920-1924 (Box 247)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 247)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 247)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 247)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 247)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 247)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 247)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 247)
  - Sta-Sth, 1928-1929 (Box 248)
  - Staa-Stan (Box 248)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 248)
    - 1917-1921 (Box 248)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 248)
  - Stadium, 1923-1926 (Box 248)
  - Staf, 1923-1937 (Box 248)
  - Staff Meeting Notice, 1928-1929 (Box 248)
  - Stan (Box 248)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 248)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 248)
    - 1930-1934 (Box 248)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 248)
  - Standard Oil Company, 1913-1914 (Box 248)
  - Standiford, Col. W.R.—ROTC (Box 248)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 248)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 248)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 248)
  - Stanford University, 1917-1937 (Box 248)
  - Stao-Staz, 1913-1923 (Box 248)
  - Star (Box 248)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 248)
    - 1928-1937 (Box 248)
  - Starr, George W., 1926-1936 (Box 248)
  - Stat, 1925-1926 (Box 248)
  - State Adjutant General, 1917 (Box 248)
  - State Attorney General, 1921 (Box 249)
  - State Auditor (Box 249)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 249)
    - 1917-1922 (Box 249)
    - 1922-1927 (Box 249)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 249)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 249)
  - State Board of Accounts (Box 249)
    - 1913-1925 (Box 249)
    - 1925-1933 (Box 249)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 249)
  - State Board of Agriculture, 1916-1917 (Box 249)
  - State Board of Charities, 1913-1931 (Box 249)
  - State Board of Charities Reports, 1928-1929 (Box 249)
  - State Board of Education (Box 249)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 249)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 249)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 249)
    - 1918-1919 (Box 249)
    - 1922-1928 (Box 249)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 249)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 249)
  - State Board of Education (Box 250)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 250)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 250)
    - September 1935-April 1936 (Box 250)
    - June-September 1936 (Box 250)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 250)
  - State Board of Field Examiners Report, 1934 (Box 250)
  - State Board of Health, 1913-1923 (Box 250)
  - State Bureau of Inspection, 1914-1917 (Box 250)
  - State Board of Medical Registration and Examination, 1915-1917 (Box 250)
  - State College Papers, 1913-1914 (Box 250)
  - State Conference of Charities and Correction, 1919-1920 (Box 250)
  - State Council of Defense, 1916-1919 (Box 250)
  - State Department of Education—vocational rehabilitation, 1934-1937 (Box 250)
  - State Department of Public Instruction (Box 250)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 250)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 250)
    - 1921-1922 (Box 250)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 250)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 250)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 250)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 250)
  - State Department of Public Instruction (Box 251)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 251)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 251)
    - September 1929-May 1930 (Box 251)
    - June-September 1930 (Box 251)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 251)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 251)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 251)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 251)
    - 1934-1936 (Box 251)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 251)
    - Division of Vocational Education (Box 251)
      - 1921-1925 (Box 251)
      - 1925-1930 (Box 251)
  - State Fire Inspection Company, 1913-1914 (Box 251)
  - State Fire Marshall, 1918-1933 (Box 251)
  - State Geologist, 1913-1915 (Box 251)
  - State, Governor of, undated (Box 251)
  - State—Joint Purchasing Committee (Box 251)